Guide to the Richard Kelly Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project files, 1939-1977; Series I
  - Ford Motor Company, 1954
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 20)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 20)
  - Fort Wayne Theater of Performing Arts, 1969
    Job location: Fort WAyne, IN
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 404)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 404)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 404)
  - Foundry Methodist Church, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 20–21)
    - Drawings (Box 20–21)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 20–21)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 20–21, Box 384)
  - Fountain Square Project, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 21)
  - Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial, 1973
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 404)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 404)
  - Franklin Savings Bank, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 21)
    - Drawings (Box 21)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 21)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 21)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 21)
    - Photographs (Box 21)
  - Freemason Street Parking Structure, 1970
    Job location: Norfolk, VA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 21)
    - Drawings (Box 21)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 21)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 21, Box 384)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 21)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 384)
  - Frick Collection, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 21)
    - Drawings (Box 21, Box 316)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 21)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 21)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 21, Box 316)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 21)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 21)
    - Photographs (Box 21, Box 404)
  - Funk, Donald Residence, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 21)
  - Gallagher and Rhoades Residence, 1958
    Job location: Bethany Beach, DE
    - Drawings (Box 237)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 237)
  - The Galleria (see also: 117 East 57th Street)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
  - Ganz Brothers, 1962
    Job location: Bergenfield, NJ
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 22)
    - Drawings (Box 257)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 257)
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Garfunkel, Arthur Apartment
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 22)
    - Drawings (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 22)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 22)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 22)
  - Gateway Center Project, 1962
    Job location: Minneapolis, MN
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 22)
  - General Motors
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 22)
    - Drawings (Box 209)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 209)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 209)
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - General Motors, Ternstedt Division, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 22)
    - Drawings (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 384)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 22)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 384)
  - Georg Jensen, Inc., 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 22)
  - Georgetown Plaza Apartments, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 22)
    - Drawings (Box 22, Box 246)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 22)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 22)
  - Gerstenfeld Residence, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 22)
    - Drawings (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 22, Box 384)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 22)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 22)
  - Gilbert, Benjamin Greenaway Island Residence, 1963
    Job location: Stamford, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 22)
    - Drawings (Box 22, Box 374)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 22, Box 374)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 22)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 22, Box 374)
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - Gilmore, Mrs. C. House, 1947
    Job location: Pleasantville, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 22)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 22)
  - Gimbel Brothers, 1949
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 22)
    - Drawings (Box 22)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 22)
  - Ginsburg Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23)
    - Drawings (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 23)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 23)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 23)
  - Girard, Alexander, 1952
    Job location: Grosse Pointe, MI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23)
  - Gitter, Josephine Apartment, 1953
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 23)
    - Material Samples (Box 23)
  - Golding, Jack garden room
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 404)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 404)
  - Gollinger, Norma Apartment
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23)
    - Drawings (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 23)
  - Good Design Exhibition, 1968
    Collaborator: Paul Rudolph
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23)
    - Drawings (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 23, Box 384)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 23)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 23)
  - Goodwin, Philip Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23)
  - Goodyear, Stephen Residence
    Job location: Darien, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23)
    - Drawings (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 23)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 23)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 23)
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Gores, Landis, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23)
  - Gorsuch, Charles, 1950
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23)
  - Gotham Development Corporation (See Also: Rizzloi Editore Corporation)
    - Drawings (Box 129, Box 314)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 314)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 129, Box 314)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 314)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 314)
  - Governor's Island (See Also: Ellis Island)
    - Drawings (Box 191)
  - Graef, Robert and Elizabeth Residence
    Job location: New Jersey
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23)
    - Drawings (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 23)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 23)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 23)
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Grand Central Building, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23)
    - Drawings (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 23)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 23, Box 384)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 23)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 23)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 23)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 23)
  - Grand Union Company, 1956
    Job location: North Brunswick, New Jersey
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 23–24)
    - Drawings (Box 23–24)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 23–24)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 23–24)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 23–24, Box 404)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 23–24)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 23–24)
  - Greenbriar Shopping Center, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
    - Drawings (Box 24, Box 128, Box 167, Box 276, Box 308)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 24, Box 167, Box 276, Box 308)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 24, Box 167, Box 276, Box 308)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 24, Box 128, Box 167, Box 308)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 128, Box 167, Box 276)
  - Greyhound Post House, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24, Box 404)
    - Drawings (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 24, Box 404)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 24)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 24)
  - Greyhound Transportation Center
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
    - Drawings (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 24)
  - Griggs, Mary Residence, 1953
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
    - Drawings (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 24)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 24)
  - Groton School
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
  - Guggenheim, Harry Residence, 1950
    Job location: Port Washington, Long Island, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
    - Drawings (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 24)
  - Guggenheim, Mrs. Solomon
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
    - Drawings (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 24)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 24)
  - Hamilton, George Residence, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
    - Drawings (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 24)
  - Hammond, Leonard Garden
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
  - Hanover Inn, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 24)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 24)
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Material Samples (Box 24)
  - Harmen Creek Coal
    - Unidentified Material (Box 26)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 26)
  - Harness Race Track, 1950
    Job location: Yonkers, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
    - Drawings (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 24)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 24)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 24)
  - Harrison, Fouilhoux, & Abramovitz, 1942
    Job location: Maine
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 24)
  - Hartung, Edward
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 24)
  - Harvard University, Eight House, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 25)
    - Drawings (Box 25)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 25)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 25)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 25)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 25)
  - Harvard Univsersity, Fogg Art Museum, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 25)
  - Harvard University, Leverett House, 1961
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 25)
    - Drawings (Box 25, Box 294)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 25)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 25)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 25)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 294)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 25, Box 294)
  - Harvard University, Leverett Library, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 25)
    - Drawings (Box 25, Box 294)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 25)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 25)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 25, Box 294)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 25, Box 294)
  - Harvard University, McKinlock Hall, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 25)
    - Drawings (Box 25, Box 294)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 25)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 25)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 25, Box 294)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 25)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 294)
  - Harvard University, Quincy House, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 26)
    - Drawings (Box 26)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 26)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 26)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 26)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 26)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 26)
  - Harvard University, Sanders Theater, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 26)
    - Drawings (Box 26)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 26)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 26)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 26)
  - Hato Ray Dispensary, 1959
    Job location: San Juan, Puerto Rico
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27)
    - Drawings (Box 27)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 27)
  - Haver, Edwin (Sculpture)
    Job location: Bethany, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 27)
  - Hawaii State Capitol
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27, Box 404)
    - Drawings (Box 205, Box 265, Box 281, Box 287, Box 312, Box 322)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 27, Box 152, Box 281)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 281, Box 312)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 119, Box 205, Box 265, Box 312, Box 322)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 205)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 205, Box 265, Box 287, Box 312, Box 322)
  - Health and Agriculture Building
    - Drawings (Box 177)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 177)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 177)
  - Hechinger Residence, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27)
    - Drawings (Box 27, Box 158)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 27)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 27)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 27, Box 158)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 158)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 27)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 158)
    - Photographs (Box 27)
  - Herzfeld, Gerald Apartment, 1953
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 27)
  - Hines, John Residence, 1950-1959
    Job location: Weston, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27)
    - Drawings (Box 27)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 27)
  - Hodgson House, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27)
    - Drawings (Box 27)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 27)
  - Hoffman, Max
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27)
    - Drawings (Box 155)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 155)
  - Hollins College, 1965
    Job location: Roanoke, VA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27)
    - Drawings (Box 27, Box 122, Box 203, Box 279, Box 283)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 27)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 27, Box 203, Box 279, Box 283)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 27, Box 203, Box 283)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 122, Box 203, Box 283)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 122)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 122)
  - Honig, Emanuel Apartment, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27)
  - Hotel America
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27)
    - Drawings (Box 27, Box 223)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 27, Box 223)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 223)
  - Hotel Manhattan, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 27)
    - Drawings (Box 27)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 27)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 27)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 27, Box 384)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 27)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 27, Box 384)
    - Photographs (Box 27)
  - Hotel Roosevelt (See Also: Roosevelt Hotel)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Drawings (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 71, Box 404)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 71, Box 404)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 71)
  - Hotel Schoeder, 1951
    Job location: Milwaukee, WI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28)
    - Drawings (Box 28)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 28)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 28)
  - Hotel St. Moritz
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28)
    - Drawings (Box 28)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 28)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 28)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 28)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 28)
  - House and Garden, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28)
  - Housen, Stanley Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28)
    - Drawings (Box 28)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 28)
  - Hoyt, Wilfred Residence, 1947
    Job location: Orange, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28)
  - Humble Oil and Refining Company, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28, Box 384)
    - Drawings (Box 28, Box 217, Box 260, Box 370)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 28, Box 217)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 28)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 28, Box 217, Box 260)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 28, Box 217, Box 260)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 28, Box 217, Box 260, Box 370)
    - Photographs (Box 28, Box 384)
  - Huston, Frederick Office Project, 1972
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28)
    - Drawings (Box 28)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 28)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 28)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 28)
  - I.E.S. (Illuminating Engineers Society) Headquarters, 1961
    - Drawings (Box 160, Box 213)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 160)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 160)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 160)
    - Material Samples (Box 160)
  - IBM (International Business Machines) Brussels International Exposition, 1958
    Job location: Belgium
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28)
    - Drawings (Box 28)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 28)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 28)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 28)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 28, Box 385)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 28)
  - IBM Chicago, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 29)
    - Drawings (Box 29)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 29, Box 385)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 29, Box 385)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 29, Box 385)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 29)
  - IBM Educational Center, 1961
    Job location: Poughkeepsie, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 29)
    - Drawings (Box 29)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 29, Box 385)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 29, Box 385)
  - IBM Kingston, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 29)
    - Drawings (Box 29)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 29)
  - IBM Miscellaneous Locations, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 29)
    - Drawings (Box 29)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 29)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 29)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 29)
  - IBM New York, World Headquarters, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 29–30)
    - Drawings (Box 29–30)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 29–30)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 29–30)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 29–30, Box 385)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 29–30)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 29–30, Box 385)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 29–30, Box 385)
    - Photographs (Box 29–30)
    - Material Samples (Box 29–30)
  - IBM Olympic Data Processing, 1960
    Job location: Squaw Valley, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 31)
    - Drawings (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 31)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 31)
  - IBM Poughkeepsie, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 31)
    - Drawings (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 31)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 31)
  - IBM Research Center, 1961
    Job location: Yorktown, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 31)
    - Drawings (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 31)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 31)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 31)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 31)
  - Independence Mall, 1954; 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 31)
    - Drawings (Box 31, Box 379, Box 385)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 31, Box 379)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 31, Box 379)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 31, Box 385)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 385)
    - Photographs (Box 31)
  - India Ambassador Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 31)
    - Drawings (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 31)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 31)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 31)
  - Inn at Roosevelt Raceway
    - Drawings (Box 220)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 220)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 220)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 220)
  - Interama, 1966
    Job location: Miami, FL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 31, Box 389)
  - International Mineral and Chemical Corporation, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 31)
    - Drawings (Box 31)
    - Photographs (Box 31)
  - Iolas Gallery, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 31)
    - Drawings (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 31)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 31)
  - Island Inn, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 31)
    - Drawings (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 31)
  - Israel Research Reactor Building, 1960
    Job location: Israel
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 31)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 31)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company
    - Drawings (Box 155, Box 220)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 155)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 155)
  - Jahncke, Ernest Lee Residence, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 32)
    - Drawings (Box 32)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 2)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 32)
  - Jay, John House, 1962
    Job location: Katonah, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 32)
    - Drawings (Box 32, Box 275, Box 378)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 32, Box 275)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 32, Box 378)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 32)
    - Photographs (Box 32)
  - Jefferson Memorial, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 32)
  - Jefferson Memorial Park (Jefferson National Expansion Memorial), 1962
    Job location: St. Louis, MO
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 32)
    - Drawings (Box 213)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 213)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 179)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 179)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 179)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 179, Box 213)
    - Photographs (Box 179)
  - Georg Jensen, Inc.
  - John F. Kennedy Educational Civic and Cultural Center, 1966
    Job location: Nassau County, NY
    Collaborator: Welton Becket
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 32)
    - Drawings (Box 377)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 377)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 377)
  - John Hancock Center. (Gen. Motors Technical Ctr.), 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 32)
    - Drawings (Box 32)